[
            {
                "question": "If you had Lafite-Rothschild on your dinner table, what would it be?",
                "options": [
                    "Juice",
                    "Wine",
                    "Water",
                    "Vodka"
                ],
                "answer": "Wine",
                "selected": ""
            },
            {
                "question": "What is sushi traditionally wrapped in?",
                "options": [
                    "Rice",
                    "Cabbage leaves",
                    "Gum",
                    "Edible seaweed"
                ],
                "answer": "Edible seaweed",
                "selected": ""            
            },
            {
                "question": "May Queen, Wisley Crab, Foxwhelps and Lane's Prince Albert are all species of what?",
                "options": [
                    "Members of the royal family",
                    "Wine",
                    "Apples",
                    "Cakes"
                ],
                "answer": "Apples",
                "selected": ""
            },
            {
                "question": "What is allspice alternatively known as?",
                "options": [
                    "Pimento",
                    "Yenibahar",
                    "Chocolate circles",
                    "Huston Rocket"
                ],
                "answer": "Pimento",
                "selected": ""
            },
            {
                "question": "What flavour is Cointreau?",
                "options": [
                    "Milk",
                    "Orange",
                    "Onion",
                    "Lime"
                ],
                "answer": "Orange",
                "selected": ""
            },
            {
                "question": "Costing around $2,600 per pound and made only to order by Knipschildt, what is the name of this chocolate truffle?",
                "options": [
                    "Mini cake",
                    "Brown mountain",
                    "Knipschildt truffle",
                    "Chocopologie"
                ],
                "answer": "Chocopologie",
                "selected": ""
            },
            {
                "question": "What colour is Absynthe?",
                "options": [
                    "Yellow",
                    "Green",
                    "Red",
                    "Blue"
                ],
                "answer": "Green",
                "selected": ""
            },
           {
                "question": "Which nuts are used in marzipan?",
                "options": [
                    "Pistachios",
                    "Almonds",
                    "Walnut",
                    "Cashew nuts"
                ],
                "answer": "Almonds",
                "selected": ""
            },
            {
                "question": "From which cactus is tequila made?",
                "options": [
                    "Aloe",
                    "Conophytum",
                    "Agave",
                    "Monantes"
                ],
                "answer": "Agave",
                "selected": ""
            },
            {
                "question": "What is called a meal in open air?",
                "options": [
                    "Open air meal",
                    "Picnic",
                    "Field treats",
                    "Lime"
                ],
                "answer": "Picnic",
                "selected": ""
            }
        ]
